ONKAR DESHMUKH

Room No.1 Shantiban CHS LTD Azad Nagar No.1, Castle Mill,

Majiwada, Thane- West

Mobile: 9730977129, 8087384437

deshmukh.onkar@yahoo.com,onkar6145@gmail.com

OVERVIEW

A highly motivated Procurement, A/R, A/P, and Collections professional with a good track record of accomplishment spanning three years. Highly creative, recognized as a results-oriented and solution-focused individual. Areas of strength include:

Accounts Payable

Problem Collections

Organizational Skills

Computer Literacy

Work as Team Player

Accounts Receivable

Communication Skills

Time Management Skills

Patient and Understanding

Quick Learner

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Commerce: Mathematics & Accounting 2008

University of Mumbai, through Bharat Collage of Commerce Badlapur Pass Class

Industrial Computer and Accounts 2010

Certification course in Industrial Accountant

Grade: A

Post Graduate Diploma

Admission Taken For PGDM (Finance) 2 Year Course In Welingkar Institute.

1st year completed.

COMPUTER SKILLS

- Tally 7.2 and 9.0
- Microsoft Office Word, Excel, PowerPoint
- Accounting Software ACE, EXGEN
- Trained on home grown ERP system at Black Magic Toners Pvt. Ltd.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

CEAT Limited(Third Party) Commercial Associate

Accounts & Vendor Reconciliation

- Accounting of Collections and follow-ups for deductions /
- other deviations.Verifying CFA Bills.
- Updating prices in master after it is duly checked by Sr. Manager.
- Preparing and circulating Overdues report for KAMs review on monthly basis
- Preparing Sales Flash

Nov 2017 - Till Date

- Monitoring GRN status of invoices billed to OEMs
- Resolving queries of OEMs on reconciliation issues guided by Manager/Sr. Manager.
- Preparing DG and Indent files.
- Coordination with Plants for dispatch of Samples.
- Monitoring Share of Business of OEMs.
- Close coordination with CFA and TLs for rejections

Ansapack Private Limited

Executive Receivables

Keeping records for PDC. (Post dated chq).

Jan 2017 - Nov 2017

- Regular Licensing with debtors.
- Preparing daily MIS for collection and outstanding payment.
- Accounting of payment received in system.
- Regular collection review by marketing persons.
- Debtors reconciliation
- Payment follow-up through mail, call, visit personally.
- Preparation of dispatched documents and related work.

EBY Fasteners

Accounts Assistant

Feb 2011- Jan 2017

- Debtors Reconciliation
- Paper work for Letter of Credit, Bills of Exchange
- Dispatch related activities: -Test Certificates, Covering Letter, Short Supplies
- 'C' Forms Management
- Preparing Bank Guarantee, Stand By Letter Of Credit, Bill of Exchange
- Solve Invoice Query Regarding Payment
- Payment Follow up with client.
- Client Visit if necessary.

Pinnacle Infrastructure International

Nov 2009 - Dec 2010

Account Executive & Administration

- Making Purchase Requisition as per requirement
- Making G.R.N(Goods Receipt Note)
- Maintain rejected material separately
- Maintain Stock(Weekly/Monthly)
- Maintain Inward & Outward Register
- Maintain MIN Production wise
- Making Consumption report as per requirement
- Co-ordination with H.O. for Vendor payment
- Handle Petty Cash & Worker Salary
- Handling workers issue(Salary, Leave)

Black Magic Toners Pvt. Ltd.

Sep 2008 - Sep 2009

Account Executive

- Making Goods Receipt Note
- Making Purchase order as per requirement

- Verification of Purchase order
- Maintain Predefined Stock Levels
- Transfer Stock from one branch to another branch
- Co-ordination with H.O. for Vendor payment
- Making Consumption report as per requirement.
- Prepare regular Sales Invoices in ERP
- Handling Petty Cash

RFERENCES

Promptly furnished upon request.